celtictuning.co.uk 2010-04-27

# Privacy Policy

Use of Personal Data 

**Use of Personal Data**

We will collect information and use it for the following purposes: 

when opening an Account and placing an order with us we need to know your name, e-mail address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and the card's expiry date. We use this information in order to process and run your Account, for credit purposes, marketing, market research and analysis and to notify you of the status of the order. 

we also ask you for your telephone number which enables us to contact you urgently in the event of there being a problem or query with your order or Account. 

should you enter a competition or other promotional feature on our website we may ask you for your name, address and e-mail address in order that we may efficiently administer the competiton and promotion as well as notifying the winners. 

we may disclose your information to other parties for the purposes of processing and fulfilling your order. 

we may also use the information that we collect from you to notify you from time to time about functionality changes to our website, the service that we provide and details of special or promotional offers. 

**Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**

We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information (data) to others. We may provide statistics or analytical records about our customers, sales, traffic patterns to reputable third party vendors but this information will not include any personally identifying information on you. 

We employ third parties and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples of these might be a courier delivering your goods to you, analysis of data, provision of marketing assistance, processing credit card payments and provision of a customer services department. Please rest assured that those companies and individuals who have access to any such personal information are not permitted to use this information for any other purposes and they are required to process any such data in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

**Transfer of Data**

The information that you enter may be transferred outside the European Economic Area for the purposes of processing and maintaining your Account with us. Any transfer of personal information outside the European Economic Area will be done so as to ensure that the information is processed only in accordance with our Privacy Policy and in strict compliance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

**Consent and Data Protection**

By using our website you irrevocably consent to authorising us to collate, collect and use this information. Any changes to our privacy policy will be updated and posted on this page of our website. 

**Opt Out**

You can opt out of e-mail updates by sending us an e-mail at [unsubscribe@celtictuning.co.uk](mailto:unsubscribe@celtictuning.co.uk) requesting that you be removed from our updates list. 

**Contact**

If you have any comments, suggestions or concerns about this Privacy Policy please e-mail [privacy@celtictuning.co.uk](mailto:privacy@celtictuning.co.uk)

|  |  Select Your Vehicle   
---  
| 

|  |   
---|---  

Can't find your vehicle? Contact Us on **(01726) 892873**  
  
Take Control! 

The eMotion self tune system allows you to tune your vehicle when and where you wish. Take control over your vehicle! Click below for more details.
